A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Dean of Graduate Studies, Convocation Programs, Series 4 FA831
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Dean of Graduate Studies, Convocation Programs, Series 4
1955-1992
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
Brink, Frank
Rockefeller University
Hirsch, James G.
FA831
1 Cubic Feet 2 boxes. Extent is approximate.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be restricted from scholarly research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment.
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be restricted from scholarly research at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/RAC Head of Reference.
Arrangement
Rockefeller University records, Dean of Graduate Studies is arranged into 3 series:
Series 2: Publications. Series 4: Convocation. Series 6: Frank Brink, Jr.
Other Finding Aids
FA224 Rockefeller University records, Dean of Graduate Studies, Publications, Series 2.
FA832 Rockefeller University records, Dean of Graduate Studies, Frank Brink, Jr., Series 6.
Conditions Governing Access note
This collection is open for scholarly research.
Biographical/Historical note
Frank Brink, Dean (1957-1972) James Hirsch, Dean (1972-)
Medical education; Medical research; Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research; Brink, Frank; Rockefeller University; Hirsch, James G.
- Convocation Programs, 1955-1992; 4; 1 Cubic Feet 2 boxes. Extent is approximate.; 1961-1964 film; 1976- tape of proceedings
  Arrangement note
  Arranged in chronological order.
  File Plan note
  Former Classification: I 380-4
  - Academic convocation (Box 1)
    - First (1959) and later years, after 1958
    - 1959, 1960, 1961 also appear in Occasional paper, 8, 9, 12, 1959-1961
  - Citations on the conferring of degrees (Box 1)
    - 1959, 1960, 1961 in Occasional papers, 8, 9, 12
    - 1962 no copy of citations
    - 1963 Rockefeller Institute Review, June 1963 only has listing
    - 1964-1968 citations in full appear in May/June issue of each year in Rockefeller Institute Review or Rockefeller University Review
    - 1969 and later years the citations appear in News and Notes
  - Silent color film Rockefeller University Convocation, 1961-1964 (Box 1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    No prints have been made. Prints must be made prior to providing any access or use of the film.
  - Includes tape of Convocation proceedings, 1976 June 9; 7 inch (Box 1)
  - Convocation, 1961 1962 1963 1964 (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents note
    ORIG. EKT. 1 Film reel. [In RAC Film Vault June 25, 1984].
  - Convocation, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Convocation, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Convocation, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Convocation, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Convocation, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Convocation, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Convocation, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Convocation, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Convocation, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Convocation, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Convocation, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 11)